LEE XIN LANG

Address: Baishiwan, Dalian Liaoning | Phone: 13614097750 | Skype: live:flyplay91

Email: flyplay91@gmail.com | LinkedIn Profile: https://www.linkedin.com/in/lee-xin-lang-a32a98153/

Full Stack Web Developer

I am a Full Stack Web Developer with over 10 years of web development experience.

My particular strength is in turning your vision into a fully functional website by writing custom web applications.

I have a lot of experience with customizing Wordpress themes and plugins and using WooCommerce. I have worked with the number of Shopify and Magento sites adding and customizing both functionality and front end.

I value good neat code that allows for a lot of flexibility.

The frontend frameworks I have particular experience with, include React, Angular, Sass, Less and of course I am highly proficient in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Jquery, etc.

On the backend, my skillset includes PHP, MySQL, Node.JS, MongoDB.

My core strengths are the MVC platforms: Laravel, Symfony, Codeigniter, and Ruby on Rails.

I am extremely detail and goal oriented and diligent about meeting deadlines while executing my client's' vision. Being a full time freelancer, I can devote myself completely to your project in order to make sure that it gets done on time, on budget and without any compromise in quality.

EXPERIENCE

08/2009 - 02/2011

SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER, CHINA UNICOM

In this company I have built company's business management websystem.

The system was purposed to manage the profits and salleries of the employees, manage HR and stocks as well as to provide good statistics system.

I also played the role of Server opts to manage the server myself.

05/2011 - 10/2013

SENIOR PROJECT MANAGER, SUNTECH

I have worked as a project manager of this company, who is running the business using eCommerce website.

The eCommerce website is built with Shopify and earning 80K of net profit per year.

I have great skills for Front-end and Back-end technology, and this website was a good play ground for me to prove my skills.

This website was built by the team with 3 members, and I gave them techincal lead to succeed the project.

PROJECT COORDINATOR, XIAOMI TECHNOLOGY

In this company I built many many significant projects using my skills on Ruby on Rails, Angular, React and PHP.

Normally each project is done by 5 or 6 members of the company, and I was proud being a top rated senior full stack web developer there.

We built the websites with various and complicated logic inside of it as well as did some online marketing works, too. The eCommerce website is built with Shopify and earning 80K of net profit per year.

I have great skills for Front-end and Back-end technology, and this website was a good play ground for me to prove my skills.

This website was built by the team with 3 members, and I gave them techincal lead to succeed the project.

EDUCATION

2005 - 2009

MASTER OF COMPUTER APPLICATIONS, BEIJING INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

SKILLS

- Frontend
 HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, jQuery, Bootstrap
 Sass, Less, AngualrJS, React
- Backend
 PHP, Ruby on Rails, Laravel, Symfony,
 Codeigniter, Node.JS

CMS
 Wordpress, Shopify, Magento, Ecommerce,
 Woocommerce

MY WEBSITES

carid.com

lulus.com

https://bushbuckoutdoors.com

https://www.fleurdumal.com

touchdolls.com

http://trafficlawheadquarters.com/

https://rtslabs.com/

http://newtosato.creazionesitoverona.it/

https://www.bandwidth.com/ https://www.getupperhand.com/ https://pleasepay.co.uk/?lang=en

https://ada.com/

https://switchvpn.net/

colaborator.com

http://ghettosoft.co/

http://pluvial.co/